Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Publishing and Business Records 1929-2005 MS 3009-RG 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1978-2005; 32 Linear feet in 32 record cartons
  - Subseries V.A. Fortune Editors on TV, 1992-2001; 15.25 Linear feet in 16 record cartons
    - Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine: Today's Business: CNBC-TV, 1995 July 19 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 25 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine' Today's Business CNBC-TV Cable July 19, 1995 7:00-8:00 AM ET 3:25". On label on case side: "'Lee Smith, Fortune Mag.' Today's Business CNBC-TV Cable July 19, 1995 7:00-8:00AM ET 3:25".
    - Brian O'Rielly, Fortune Magazine: Busted Boomers: Eyewitness News: WABC-TV (ABC) New York, 1995 July 19 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 54 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Brian O'Rielly, Fortune Magazine/Busted Boomers' Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York July 19, 1995 11:00-11:30 PM 2:54". On label on case side: "'Brian O'Rielly. Fortune Magazine/Busted Boomers' Eyewitness News WABC_TV (ABC) New York July 19, 1995 11:00-11:30PM 2:54".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: CBS For Sale: Eyewitness News: WABC-TV (ABC) New York, 1995 July 21 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 28 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine/CBS For Sale' Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York July 21, 1995 5:00-6:00 PM 2:28". On label on case side: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine/CBS For Sale' Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York 7/21/95 5:00 PM 2:28".
    - John Curran: Disney Merger: WABC-TV, 1995 July 31 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "John Curran - Disney Merger - WABC-TV, 7-31-95".
    - John Curran: Disney Merger: WABC-TV, 1995 July 31 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 10)
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Disney Merger: Eyewitness News: WABC-TV (ABC) New York, 1995 July 31 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 30 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine' Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York July 31, 1995 5:00-6:00 PM 3:30". On label on case side: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York 7/31/95 5:00 PM 3:30 Disney Merger".
    - Strat Sherman: CBS Takeover: Charlie Rose Show, 1995 July 31 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Strat Sherman- CBS Takeover - Charlie Rose, 7-31-95".
    - Start Sherman: CBS Takeover: Charlie Rose Show, 1995 July 31 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Strat Sherman- CBS Takeover- Charlie Rose, 7-31-95".
    - Stratford Sherman, Fortune: Disney Merger: Charlie Rose Show: PBS-TV, 1995 July 31 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (10 min., 42 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Stratford Sherman, Fortune /Disney Merger' Charlie Rose PBS-TV Network July 31, 1995 11:00-12:00 AM ET 10:42". Sticker on case front: "4". On label on case side: "'Stratford Sherman, Fortune/ Disney Merger' Charlie Rose PBS-TV Network 7/31/95 11:00 PM ET 10:42".
    - John Huey, Fortune Magazine: Disney Merger: Good Morning America: ABC-TV, 1995 August 1 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (5 min., 52 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Huey, Fortune Magazine' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network August 1, 1995 7:00-9:00 AM ET 5:52". On label on case side: "John Huey, Fortune Magazine" Good Morning America ABC-TV Network 8/01/95 7:00 AM ET 5:52 Disney Merger".
    - Strat Sherman: Westinghouse/CBS Merger: NY1, 1995 August 4 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Strat Sherman 8/4/95--NY1 Westinghouse/CBS Merger Bill Carter-NYT Max Frankel-NYT"
    - Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine: Fox News: KRIV-TV (Fox) Houston, 1995 August 8 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (31 sec.): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine' Fox News 7 A.M. KRIV-TV (Fox) Houston August 8, 1995 7:00-8:00 AM :31". On label on case side: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine' Fox News 7 A.M. KRIV-TV (Fox) Houston 8/8/95 7:00-8:00 AM :31".
    - Strat Sherman: Discusses Ovitz Named President of Disney: WNBC-TV, 1995 August 14 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Strat Sherman, 8/14/95, WNBC-TV Discusses Ovitz named President of Disney".
    - Geoff Colvin: Discusses ADM Marc Whitacre: Nightly Business Report, 1995 August 14 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Geoff Colvin, 8/14/95, Nightly Business Report, Discusses ADM Marc Whitacre".
    - Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine: Mark Whitacre: Nightly Business Report: PBS-TV, 1995 August 14 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 29 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine/Mark Whitacre' Nightly Business Report PBS-TV Network August 14, 1995 6:30-7:00 PM ET 2:29". On label on case side: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Mag/ Mark Whitacre' Nightly Business Report PBS-TV Network 8/14/95 6:30 PM ET 2:29".
    - Fortune Magazine: Mark Whitacre: Moneyline: Cable News Network, 1995 August 14 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (40 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine/Mark Whitacre" Moneyline Cable News Network August 14, 1995 7:00-7:30 PM ET 0:40". On label on case side: "'Fortune Magazine/Mark Whitacre Moneyline Cable News Network 8/14/95 7:00 PM ET 0:40".
    - Stratford Sherman, Fortune Magazine: Michael Ovitz: News 4 New York: WNBC-TV (NBC) New York, 1995 August 14 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 26 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Stratford Sherman, Fortune Magazine/Michael Ovitz' News 4 New York WNBC-TV (NBC) New York August 14, 1995 11:00-11:30 PM 2:26". On label on case side: "Stratford Sherman, Fortune Mag/Michael Ovitz" News 4 New York WNBC-TV (NBC) New York 8/14/95 11:00 PM 2:26"
    - John Curran: Today Show: August 14, 1995 August 14-17 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "John Curran Date: 8/17/95 Title: Today Show 8/14/95 Show: TDY Editor: TVY DVRS of Beta Tdy Show 8/4/95 5-6 Dub Feed Location: EJ13 Mixed CH 1 and 2". On label on case side: "John Curran Today Show 8/14/95 (Dub)". On label on cassette: "Title: John Curran TDY 8/14/95 Date: 8/17/95 Editor: TM".
    - Mark Whitcare: Fortune Magazine: TV Food News and Views: TCFN-TV, 1995 August 17 (Offsite-box 2920, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (38 sec.): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "'Mark Whitcare -- Fortune Magazine' TV Food News and Views TVFN-TV (Cable) August 17, 1995 6:00-7:00 PM :38". On label on case side: "8/17/95--ADM/Fortune Cited on TV Food New and Views".
    - Archer Daniel Midland: Wand News: WAND-TV (ABC), 1995 August 22 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (39 sec.): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Archer Daniels Midland/Fortune Magazine WAND News WAND-TV (ABC) Decatur August 22, 1995 6:00PM :39". On label on case side: "Archer Daniels Midland / Fortune Magazine | August 22, 1995". On label on cassette: "Archer Daniels Midland/Fortune Magazine August 22. 1995".
    - Mark Whitacre: Channel 3 News: WCIA-TV (CBS) Champaign, 1995 August 22 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 9 sec.): On label on case and cassette: "'ADM-Mark Whitacre/Fortune Magazine' Channel 3 News WCIA-TV (CBS) Champaign August 22, 1995 5:00-5:30 PM 1:09".
    - Susan Kuhn: CNN Sunday Morning: Cable News Network, 1995 August 27 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (7 min., 48 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Susan, Kuhn/Fortune Magazine' CNN Sunday Morning Cable News Network August 27, 1995 7:00-10:00 AM ET 7:48". Sticker on case front "z". On label on case side: "'Susan, Kuhn, Fortune Mag.' CNN Sunday Morning Cable News Network 8/27/95 7:00 AM ET 7:48".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Bank Merger: Today: NBC-TV, 1995 August 28 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 44 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: " "John Curran, Fortune Magazine/Bank Merger" Today NBC-TV Network August 28, 1995 7:00-9:00 AM ET 1:44". On label on case side: " "John Curran, Fortune Mag./Bank Merger" Today NBC-TV Network August 28, 1995 7:00 AM ET 1:44".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Channel 11 News at Ten: WPIX-TV (IND) New York, 1995 August 28 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 16 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine' Channel 11 News at Ten WPIX-TV (IND) New York August 28, 1995 10:00-11:00 PM 2:16". On label on case side: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine' Channel 11 News at Ten WPIX-TV (IND) New York 8/28/95 10:00 PM 2:16".
    - Ann Reilly Dowd, Fortune Magazine: CEO's Choice for President: Today's Business: CNBC-TV, 1995 August 29 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 5 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Ann Reilly Dowd, Fortune Magazine/CEO's Choice for President' Today's Business CNBC-TV Cable August 29, 1995 7:00-8:00 AM ET 3:05". On label on case side: "Ann Reilly Dowd CNBC - 8-29-95 Learning to live with Newt".
    - Fortune Magazine Poll/Gingrich: Good Morning America: ABC-TV Network, 1995 August 30 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (21 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine/Gingrich' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network August 30, 1995 7:00-9:00 AM ET 0:21". On label on case side: "'Fortune Mag. Poll/Gingrich' Good Morning America ACB-TV Network 8/30/95 7:00-9:00 AM ET 0:21".
    - Betsy Morris, Fortune Magazine: Female Executive Burnout: The Money Wheel: C N B C, 1995 August 31 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (4 min., 5 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Betsy Morris, Fortune Magazine/ Female Executive Burnout' The Money Wheel C N B C August 31, 1995 2:00-3:00 PM ET 4:05". On label on case side: "'Betsy Morris, Fortune Magazine Female Executive Burnout' The Money Wheel CNBC 8/31/95 2:00 PM ET 4:05".
    - Betsy Morris: Women's Midlife Crisis: The Money Wheel and Good Morning America, 1995 August 31 - September 4 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Betsy Morris: The Money Wheel 8/31/95 Good Morning America 9/4/95 Women's Midlife Crisis".
    - Betsy Morris: Good Morning America, 1995 September 4 (Offsite-box 2921, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case front and side: "Betsy Morris: Good Morning America September 4, 1995".
    - Betsy Morris, Fortune Magazine: Female Executive Burnout: Good Morning America: ABC-TV, 1995 September 4 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic)(5 min., 53 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Betsy Morris, Fortune Magazine/Female Executive Burnout' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network September 4, 1995 7:00-9:00 AM ET 5:53". On label on case side: "'Betsy Morris, Fortune Magazine Female Executive Burnout' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network 9/4/95 7:00 AM ET 5:53".
    - Alex Taylor, Fortune Magazine: Ten O'Clock News: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1995 September 8 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 57 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Alex Taylor, Fortune Magazine' Ten O'Clock News WNYW-TV (Fox) New York September 8, 1995 10:00-11:00 PM 1:57". On label on case side: "'Alex Taylor, Fortune Mag' Ten O'Clock News WNYW-TV (Fox) New York Septemer 8, 1995 10:00 PM 1:57".
    - Ross Perot/NAFTA: Moneyline: Cable News Network, 1995 September 18 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (12 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Ross Perot/Fortune Magazine NAFTA' Moneylone Cable News Network September 18, 1995 7:00-7:30 PM ET 12:00". On label on case side: "'Ross Perot/Fortune Magazine NAFTA' Moneyline Cable News Network 9/18/95 7:00 PM ET 12:00".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Ratting on your Boss: New York Today: WNBC-TV, 1995 September 19 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 20 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine/Ratting On Your Boss' New York Today WNBC-TV Network September 19, 1995 5:30-7:00 AM 2:20". On label on case side: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine/ Ratting On Your Boss' New York Today WNBC-TV (NBC) New York 9/19/95 5:30 AM 2:20".
    - Rob Norton Interview: Fortune Business Report, 1995 September 28 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Rob Norton Interview Raw Footage 9/28". On label on case side: "Rob Norton Fortune Business Report 9-28-95 -Raw-".
    - David Kirkpatrick, Fortune Magazine: Interview Clips, 1995 October (Offsite-box 2922, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on cover and cassette front: "David Kirkpatrick Fortune Magazine Interview Clips". On label on cassette side: "David Kirkpatrick on TV October/1995".
    - Susan Kuhn, Fortune: Retirement: CNN Saturday Morning: Cable News Network, 1995 October 21 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (6 min., 57 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Susan Kuhn, Fortun Magazine/Retirement' CNN Saturday Morning Cable News Network October 21, 1995 7:00-10:00 AM ET 6:57". Sticker on case front: "1". On label on case side: "'Susan Kuhn, Fortune Magazine/ Retirement' CNN Saturday Morning Cable News Network 10/21/95 7:00 AM ET 6:57".
    - Geoffrey Colvin: Best Cities: CNN, 1995 October 24 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Geoffrey Colvin on CNN -- Best Cities 10/24/95".
    - Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine: CNN Morning News: Cable News Network, 1995 October 24 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (7 min., 35 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine' CNN Morning News Cable News Network October 24, 1995 9:00-10:00 AM ET 6:30 CNN Morning News Cable News Network October 24, 1995 10:00-11:00 AM ET 1:05". On label on case side: "Geoffrey Colvin" CNN Morning News Cable News Network 10/24/95 9:00-10:00AM 6:30 10/24/95 10:00-11:00AM 1:05".
    - Fortune Magazine/Best Cities: Today Show: NBC-TV, 1995 October 25 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 36 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine/Best Cities' Today Show NBC-TV Network October 25, 1995 7:00-9:00 AM ET 2:36". On label on case side: "'Fortune Magazine/Best Cities' Today Show NBC-TV Network 10/25/95 7:00 AM ET 2:36". Includes a note from the cassette producer indicating that the contents of the tape are grainy.
    - Best Cities for Business: Reuters Interviews Michael Weatherseed, 1995 October 26 (Offsite-box 2922, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Best Cities for Business Reuters Interviews Michael Weatherseed -- 10/26/95".
    - Michael Weatherseed, Fortune: Reuters Business Morning Focus, 1995 October 26 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label: "10/26/1995 26/10/95 Reuters Business Morning Focus Michael Weather seed 'Fortune'".
    - Suzanne Barlyn: Fortune Magazine Best Cities: World News Asia: CNN-International/Cable, 1995 October 27 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (4 min., 42 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine Best Cities/ Suzanne Barlyn World News Asia CNN-International/ Cable October 27, 1995 8:00-8:30AM 4:42". On label on case side: "'Suzanne Barlyn/ Best Cities' World News Asia CNN-International/ Cable October 27, 1995 8-8:30AM 4:42".
    - Suzzane Boylan, Fortune Magazine: Good Day Wake-Up: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1995 November 6 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 22 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Suzzane Boylan, Fortune Magazine' Good Day Wake-Up WNYW-TV (Fox) New York November 6, 1995 5:30-6:00 AM 3:22". On label on case side: "'Suzanne (Boylan)----Barlyn?, Fortune Mag' Good Day Wake-Up WNYW-TV (Fox) New York 11/06/95 5:30 AM 3:22".
    - Forbes vs. Fortune:The Money Wheen: CNN-TV, 1995 November 22 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (45 sec.): On labels on case and cassette: "'Forbes vs. Fortune' The Money Wheel CNBC-TV Cable November 22, 1995 12:30-1:00 PM ET 0:45".
    - 1995 Best Cities: Singapore Press Conference: TCS News, 1995 November 23 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on cassette side: "Singapore Press Conf. TCS News 23.11.95 English 1995 Best Cities". On label on cassette front: "TCS News English 23.11.95"
    - David Kirkpatrick, Fortune Magazine: Internet: The Computer Chronicles: PBS-TV, 1995 November 29 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (40 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'David Kirkpatrick, Fortune Magazine/Internet' The Computer Chronicles PBS-TV Network November 29, 1995 2-2:30 PM :40". On label on case side: "David Kirkpatrick discusses the internet in PBS's The Computer Chronicles 11/29/95".
    - Archer/Daniels Midland/Fortune Magazine: NBC Nightly News: NBC-TV, 1995 November 29 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (4 min., 17 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Archer/Daniels Midland/Fortune Magazine' NBC Nightly News NBC-TV Network November 29, 1995 6:30-7:00 PM ET 4:17". On label on case side: "'Archer/Daniels Midland/Fortune Magazine' NBC Nightly News NBC-TV Network 11/29/95 6:30 PM ET 4:17".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Investors Guide, 1995 December 5-23 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-Matic) (10 min., 46 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine/Investors Guide' Various Coverage December 5 - 23, 1995 (Schedule Enclosed)". On label on case side: "Fortune John Curran 1996 Investor Guid. Compilation Tape 12/5-23, 1995".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Investors Guide, 1995 (Offsite-box 2923, Folder 1)
      Originally enclosed with John Curran, Fortune Magazine: Investors Guide, Box 2923 Item 8. Included in this file is a list of the the contents which has the title of shows and channels where appearances were made, the time of the appearance, the date of the appearance, and the length of the segment.
    - Marshall Loeb, Fortune Magazine: Unemployment: Good Day New York: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1995 December 12 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (5 min. 35 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Marshall Loeb, Fortune Magazine/Unemployment' Good Day New York WNYW-TV (Fox) New York December 12, 1995 6:00-7:00 AM 5:35". On label on case side: "'Marshall Loeb, Fortune Mag/ Unemployment' Good Day New York WNYW-TV (Fox) New York 12/12/95 6am".
    - Susan Kuhn, Fortune Magazine: Corporate Glass Cielings: News 10 AM: KXTV-TV (ABC) Sacramento, 1995 December 18 (Offsite-box 2923, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 46 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "'Corporate Glass Ceilings/Susan Kuhn, Fortune Magazine' News 10 AM KXTV-TV (ABC) Sacramento December 18, 1995 6:00-7:00AM 3:46". On label on case side: "Dec. 18, 1995 -- Susan Kuhn Discusses Glass-Ceiling KXTV-TV Sacramento 3:46".
    - John Huey: Moneyline: CNN, 1995 December 25 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on case side: "John Huey on CNN's Moneyline 12/25/95-Discusses 1995 bix events w. Shephard, Michaels". On label on cassette: "John Huey on CNN's Moneyline, 12-25-95"
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Master Tape, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Master Tape - 1995 Fortune Editors on TV".
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Master Tape, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Folder 1)
      This folder contains a label which fell off Fortune Editors on TV: Master Tape, Box 2924 Item 2. The label was moved to a folder since the cassette itself has no case and is loose. On the label: "Fortune Editors on TV Master Tape 1995".
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Master Tape, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (Small Betacam SP): On label on case front: "MASTER Tape 1995 Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs". On label on case side: "MASTER 1995 Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV"
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Master Tape, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. Written on case: "Rough Cut". On label on cassette front: "Fortune Magazine 1)Fortune Editors on TV 2)Geoffrey Colvin on TV". On label on cassette side: "MASTER Tape 1995 Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV">
    - Geoffrey Colvin on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "1995 Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV Executive Editor Fortune Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs". On label on case side: "1995 Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV Executive Editor Fortune".
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case: 1995 Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs". On label on case side: "Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV".
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Folder 2)
      Originally enclosed with Fortune Editors on TV, Box 2924 Item 6. The folder contains a note which lists of those included on the tape, their position with Fortune, and the topics they covered in their appearances.
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV 1995 Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs". On label on case side: "Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV 1995". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV".
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Folder 3)
      Originally enclosed with Fortune Editors on TV, Box 2924 Item 7. The folder contains a note which lists of those included on the tape, their position with Fortune, and the topics they covered in their appearances.
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "1995 Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs". On label on case side: "1995 Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Fortune Editors on TV".
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Folder 4)
      Originally enclosed with Fortune Editors on TV, Box 2924 Item 8. The folder contains a note which lists of those included on the tape, their position with Fortune, and the topics they covered in their appearances.
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 9)
    - Fortune Editors on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Folder 5)
      Originally enclosed with Fortune Editors on TV, Box 2924 Item 9. The folder contains a note which lists of those included on the tape, their position with Fortune, and the topics they covered in their appearances.
    - Geoffrey Colvin On TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 10)